dgmaxinteractive.com 2012-03-19

# DGMAX Interactive – Performance Based Marketing

## 

Your privacy is important to DGMAX Interactive and we are committed to protecting the privacy of our members. This statement discloses the information practices including what information is gathered and how information is used.

**Personally Identifiable Information**  
DGMAX Interactive does not share, disclose or sell any personally identifiable information regarding its clients or publishers. DGMAX Interactive will not collect any personal information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. Examples of such information are: name, postal address, company, e-mail address, phone number, fax number, user id, and password. User I.D.s and passwords may be used to give you member access to certain areas of our website.

**How We Collect Information**  
DGMAX Interactive collects information from its users as users contact us via contact forms, or apply to participate in our Performance based marketing programs. 

DGMAX Interactive also may use "cookies" (A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive.) and similar technology to obtain information about your visits to our sites or your responses to e-mail from us - both individually and in aggregated data that does not identify you. These reporting tools tell us the parts of our web sites or e-mails in which you showed an interest or took some action, and help us improve the quality and usefulness of our sites.

**How We Use Information**  
DGMAX Interactive does not sell or purchase Web user information that is personally identifiable. All personal information that is collected by DGMAX Interactive is intended for internal use only. This includes information such as Contact Name, Address, Email and etc. DGMAX Interactive uses the personally identifiable information we collect online mainly to provide you with the services you have inquired about and to let you know about other offerings, which may be of interest to you. US publisher's information such as tax ID may be used so that total commissions earned can be reported to the appropriate taxation authorities. None-personally identifiable information such as visited URLs, IP addresses, cookies shown, date/time of visit and etc. is collected from Web users to assist in the proper function of our service as well as the targeting of advertisements from our customers and the reporting of combined data to both advertisers and publishers. Advertisers may implore third-party service providers that collect anonymous user visit information, DGMAX Interactive cannot be held responsible for the actions of third parties or their privacy practices as we have no control over the information collected. DGMAX Interactive uses vendors to carry out certain functions in marketing and delivering services to you, and so shares online data with those vendors to the extent necessary for them to perform their work. Such partners and vendors must use that personally identifiable information only for the purposes for which it was shared and protect it from any further use.  

**Children's Privacy**  
DGMAX Interactive is extremely sensitive on the issue of children's privacy and strives to protect the privacy of children using the Internet. The Site, products, and services are not developed for or directed at children. Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to do business with us. We do not collect personal information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13. Should we come to know of a certain user who has registered with us is under the minimum required age, we will remove the user immediately.

**External links**  
DGMAX Interactive Web sites may contain links to other Web sites. DGMAX Interactive is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those other Web sites.

**Security**  
We use encryption, firewalls and other technology and security procedures to help protect the accuracy and security of your personal information and prevent unauthorized access or improper use.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
We recommend that you periodically review this Privacy Policy, because it may be updated from time to time. In case of change, all changes will be posted on this current page.

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web site please contact us.
